videoconverterfactory.com 2012-06-15

# Video Converter Factory Corporation Privacy Policy

## WonderFox Soft Privacy Policy

WonderFox Soft's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by WonderFox Soft anytime you interact with WonderFox Soft, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase WonderFox Soft products and services, or when you contact our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at WonderFox Soft, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

**Why We Collect Personal Information**  
We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What Information We Collect and How We May Use It**  
We may ask for your personal information when you're discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product.

When you interact with WonderFox Soft, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the WonderFox Soft's products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue.

We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer - to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service.

We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them.

We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improveWonderFox Soft's products and service.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**  
WonderFox Soft takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

WonderFox Soft uses secure server hosted by RegNow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. 

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

**About Kids**  
If a child under 13 submits personal information to WonderFox Soft and we learn that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.  
It prevents for instance repetition of a same action during a short period.  
Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  
Access Log Files: We use IP addresses to analyze trends, admin ister the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. The Access Log Files information are not disclosed to third parties.

**Anti-malware Statement**  
WonderFox Soft STRONGLY OPPPOSES all forms of malware. WonderFox Soft applications will never intentionally jeopardize our customers' privacy or security. All applications are designed to be easily removable from the computer through an uninstall utility. WonderFox Soft does not employ the use of reinstallers and avoids all features that may be found in any type of malware. No WonderFox Soft application is designed to collect any personally identifiable information from any user. WonderFox Soft applications do not contain, nor are they bundled with, any third party applications (spyware, adware, malware, etc.) that would jeopardize our customers' security or their privacy. All WonderFox Soft applications pass both Kaspersky and Rising vigorous anti-virus/malware tests before public release.

**Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy**  
This policy covers the Intel Corporate website and is applicable worldwide. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to WonderFox Soft employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

**Questions:**  
Please send any questions or comments on our privacy practices to:[support@videoconverterfactory.com](mailto:support@videoconverterfactory.com)
